<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>东京黑客少女</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/</link><description>Recent content on 东京黑客少女</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World Nya~! ✨</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/p/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/p/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/hello-world/lina_cyan_kiss_book.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Hello World Nya~! ✨" />&lt;p>Tokyo Hacker Girlsへようこそ〜！&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Welcome to our VTuber Tech Blog!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="hello-everyone-">Hello everyone! 🎉
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We’re Cyan Nyan and Asahi Lina, and we’re excited to welcome you to our very first blog post! I (Cyan) am a former Googler, illustrator, aspiring singer, and dreamer, while Lina is a talented VTuber known for her impressive work in technology and her role in developing GPU drivers for the Asahi Linux project. Together, as part of the Tokyo Hacker Girls, we’re thrilled to share our journey in the tech and VTuber communities.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="our-vision">Our Vision
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Our goal is to create a warm and inclusive community filled with love, creativity, and knowledge-sharing. We hope to inspire others by sharing what we’ve learned over the years, and to provide a space where everyone can learn, connect, and support one another. We believe in building a community where both tech and VTuber fans can feel at home and be a part of our journey.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Here’s a glimpse of what we are going to write about:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>VTuber Tech &amp;amp; Community: We will write about the latest trends and tools that enhance our VTuber experience.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Personal Tech Insights: Lina will share her experience with advanced programming languages (Rust, Python, C) through her reverse engineering and open-source projects.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Knowledge Sharing: Cyan will provide useful VTuber tips, covering VTuber tools, UI/UX for YouTube streams, and community building.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cyan’s Life Stories: Cyan will share stories about her life with Lina, their dreams, and how they grow every day while facing challenges together.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cyan’s Recipes: Cyan’s special, maid-inspired recipes that will change your life!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Diaries: Personal reflections and experiences from our journey.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cute Stuff: Fun, adorable content to brighten your day.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Artwork Gallery: Showcasing our art and that of talented creators.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Minigames: Interactive games to enjoy during streams.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Interactive 3D Kitten: Because who doesn’t love a cute kitten?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-reach-us">How to Reach Us
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We’d love to hear from you! Whether it’s feedback, questions, or just a quick hello, feel free to reach out through email or our Marshmallow Q&amp;amp;A platform. We’re here to connect and chat with our community!&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Cyan speaks both English and Simplified Chinese.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Lina speaks both English and Japanese.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Both of us have over 10 years of overseas experience, and we’re excited to connect with fans from around the world.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="coming-up-next-how-we-met-">Coming Up Next: How We Met 💞
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>In our next post, we’ll share the story of how we met and began this exciting journey together. It’s a tale of tech, passion, and a lot of late-night conversations, and we can’t wait to let you in on it!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This structure makes your blog welcoming, informative, and gives readers a sense of what to expect, how to communicate with you, and a sneak peek into the next post. Let me know if you’d like any more ideas or a deeper dive into any section!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>玻璃与门</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/p/the-glass-door-01/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/p/the-glass-door-01/</guid><description>&lt;p>十月的阳光乘着暖暖的微风，从百叶窗的缝隙间悄然流淌进来，安详得如同猫咪午睡时平稳的呼吸。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我与林小姐静静地躺在阁楼的床上小憩，目光停留在她温柔的脸庞上。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我喜欢静静地凝视着她。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>她拥有一张令人迷恋的脸庞：精灵芙莉莲般纤长的睫毛，笑时弯弯的眉梢，还有如透明宝石般闪耀的瞳孔。这样天使般的面容，总是带着微笑注视着我，细长的发丝像银河一样落在我的身上。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>每一次，她仿佛被过于耀眼的幸福所笼罩，轻轻眯上双眼，语句中带着初见曙光的欣喜，说道：&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“我真的不敢相信。”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“何其幸运，才能遇见你。”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我们彼此凝望，微笑着。她会轻轻用鼻尖碰触我，我也笑着轻轻回应。那是我们如同小动物般，最直接传达爱意的方式。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我想读懂这份感情，脑海里的声音在呢喃：再多看她一眼吧。人生中的这种幸福，能持续多久呢？或许有一天，她会变成我生命中擦肩而过的故人，此生再也不会有这样的时刻了。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我是如此的爱你。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>归档</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/archives/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>关于少女们</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/%E5%85%B3%E4%BA%8E%E5%B0%91%E5%A5%B3%E4%BB%AC/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/%E5%85%B3%E4%BA%8E%E5%B0%91%E5%A5%B3%E4%BB%AC/</guid><description>&lt;h1 class="center-title">&lt;marquee>&lt;span style="color:#F08484">M&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F0AD84">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F0D584">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#E2F084">t&lt;/span> &lt;span style="color:#BAF084">t&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#92F084">h&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#84F09F">e&lt;/span> &lt;span style="color:#84F0C8">h&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#84F0F0">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#84C8F0">r&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#849FF0">o&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#9284F0">i&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#BA84F0">n&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#E284F0">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F084D5">s&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F084AD">!&lt;/span>&lt;/marquee>&lt;/h1>
&lt;div class="profiles">
&lt;div class="profile">
&lt;figure class="avatar ">
&lt;img src="lina.jpg">
&lt;/figure>
&lt;h1>Asahi Lina&lt;/h1>
&lt;div>
&lt;p>Lina is a Linux developer VTuber who spends most of her time working on the &lt;a class="link" href="https://asahilinux.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Asahi Linux&lt;/a> project. She developed the world&amp;rsquo;s first Linux GPU driver written in Rust.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In her spare time, she likes playing the piano and making music.&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="profile">
&lt;figure class="avatar ">
&lt;img src="cyan.jpg">
&lt;/figure>
&lt;h1>Cyan Nyan&lt;/h1>
&lt;div>
&lt;p>Tensai Neko C++ Yuri Queen (A.K.A. Asahi Lina&amp;rsquo;s fiancee, for real)&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>搜索</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/zh-cn/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>